1. openBrowser(URL)
5. custom.BrowserHelper.setupBrowserWindow()
9. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
13. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/track your order"))
17. setText(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/txtField_Email"), "agung.priyadi@gtech.digital")
21. setText(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/txtField_Verification Code"), "")
25. click(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/btn_Send"))
29. verifyTextPresent("The verification code has been sent, please check in the mailbox.", false)
1. status = testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus()
5. if (status == "PASSED")
2. saveScreenshot("FAILED")
1. tcName = getTestCaseName()
1. return com.kms.katalon.core.configuration.RunConfiguration.getExecutionSourceName().replace(Test Cases/, ).replaceAll([\\/:*?"<>|], _)
5. folderPath = Screenshot/$status/$tcName/
9. Files.createDirectories(Paths.get(folderPath))
13. screenshotPath = $folderPath$status_$this.getTimestamp().png
1. return new java.text.SimpleDateFormat(yyyyMMdd_HHmmss).format(new java.util.Date())
17. takeScreenshot(screenshotPath)
21. println("Screenshot saved : " + screenshotPath)